hello, a very warm welcome to all of you
on my YouTube channel. In today's video,
we will do a comparison between two health
insurance plans, the one for Cooker
's Help Them In and the one for HTC and the one for
Suraksha. Please watch this video till the end
because in this video I will give
you information regarding health issues
which will be very useful for you in your life
and those who
want to join health insurance or are already associated with Speed,
they can also contact us through this channel
and
can listen. So let's start the
video. First of all, we will know
what is the difference between these plans, what are the things that
make people different from each other, so first of all let's
talk about Someshwar
options, I am uncle Lakhan Lal, in this you get
coverage options ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs 1 crore and
in Suraksha plan you get coverage options ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs
75 lakh. In
both the plans, you get Priyanka along with
additional expenses in which
In companies you get free hated reaction cover
for 30 days and post graduation
you get free hospitalization cover for 7 days and for
spreading hatred you get free hospitalization cover
for 7 days and if you have post graduation you get free hospitalization cover
for 180 days now road emergency
ambulance provide on this you get
cover in help complaint from
₹3000 and in Suraksha plan you get from
2000 to rs.15000 along with this 2
to ₹500 Dharti Air Ambulance that you get this
curvature admit, there are benefits of hospital test in
city company Islam you get
₹1000 on discount and ₹4000
in birthday plan you get hospital additional optional home cover
from ₹1000 on rs.7000 and now we will
talk at 2 p.m.  Friends, the decision of the bonus is to help them,
you get a bonus of 20 percent per year
which goes up
to 100 percent in every year. The bonus is
never reduced in Max Bupa. In the
same way, in the Suraksha plan, you get a
relative adult benefit of 10 percent
which goes up to
275 percent.
In the first plan, you also get a health checkup. On Thursday, you can
ask for a preventive health checkup benefit.
Friends, we have talked about the
difference between the two plans. We
will talk about this in this reply.
But
now we are talking about the infection treatment
expenses. Now let's talk about the
screenshot. Now let's talk about the
treatment cover. In both plans,
you get all the treatment covers.
Along with positive treatment,
you get an award in 1627.
You also get a cut on all domestic and hydration expenses. Apart from these,
you get both the other benefits. In the
live video,  You
get tax benefits, you get
under section 15, you get free look period of 15 days,
you get cancellation
facility, now we will talk about
those benefits which are available to you only in Max Bupa
health companies, you get the
benefit of vegetables as an additional option,
which is available to you in Help Balance plan from one lakh to
10 lakh rupees, if we
talk about the benefits then in this Bhopal company,
you get Animals like and Raju in OPD from
two and a half thousand to seven and a half
thousand rupees, now we will talk
about the benefits of Max Bupa, which
you get in this company, which you cannot
subscribe after joining your policy, which
you do not get subscribed,
from 15th August till the time of Cardiac
Prevent, you get the benefit of 7 minutes and Vivaan
-
you get the benefit on Active, apart from these policies, you
also get some option covers
in good amazing protection work like
pen drive cover, Bhushan you get  In which
you get delivery expenses ranging from 15000 to 75,000 rupees. You get post certain extent of delivery.
You get two front care, common
infertility treatment, Vyaghra Tovar,
in which you have normal delivery. Now you
get 50% option share option, so
you get subscribe notification option from 5000 to 15 thousand, in which you
can use your routine and
you get medical expenses, if you get subscription
then it goes up to maximum, which is
available in my kitchen.
Maintenance option from 10 percent to 25 percent is available. Now we will talk
about the waiting period of these France, which
is approximately 100% in implants.
For this you have a waiting period of 24 months.
For pimples you have a
waiting period of 36 months. In protection,
you have a waiting period of 4 years in period cover.
Friends, tell us through this information and
comments how it helps you in increasing your speed.
Subscribe and if you like this video then
you can share this video with your relatives, it will
help them and don't
forget to subscribe to my channel,
like the video so that my
motivation remains the same and I will keep bringing
such informative videos for you,
press the bell icon so that
you get the updates of my latest videos first,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]
Kar Do Hua Hai